I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
South Park - Season 11 Episode 5 "Fantastic Easter Special" "复活节特别节目"
双语合成 Lv&daisy
...In my Easter Bonnet, with all the frills upon it,
I'll be the grandest lady in the Easter parade.
看这个, 哈?
Look at that one, huh?
一半紫,一半黄,还有环状的花纹
Half purple and half yellow with a chikadee sticker.
太棒了.
I'm good.
恩, 能问个问题吗?
Uh, can I ask a question?
为什么我们要干这个?
Why do we do this?
什么...你什么意思, "为什么我们要干这个?" 因为是复活节(Easter)啊 !
Wha... what do you mean, "Why do we do this?" It's Easter!
对, 那么, 为什么我们给蛋涂上颜色?
Right, so, why do we color eggs?
呃,这样复活节兔子(Easter bunny) 就能把它们藏起来了
Wulll, ssso that the Easter bunny can hide them.
是啊, 但是为什么呢?
Yeah, but why?
Stanley, 复活节是用来庆祝 耶稣复活的那一天的
Stanley, Easter celebrates the day that Jesus was resurrected
就在替我们赎罪 而被钉死在十字架上之后
after being crucified for our sins.
所以我们把蛋放进用彩色的醋里 然后一只巨大的兔子就可以把它们藏起来了?
So we dip eggs in colored vinegar and a giant rabbit hides them?
就是这样.
That's right.
你没发现这里面有点逻辑错误吗?
You don't see the missteps in logic with that?
你看, 我是说耶稣死在十字架上
Look, I'm just saying that somewhere between Jesus dying on the Cross
和一只兔子藏鸡蛋 这之间好象没什么联系.
and a giant bunny hiding eggs there seems to be a, a gap of information.
Stanley, 只管涂好你的蛋!
Stanley, just dye your Goddamned eggs!
我不喜欢涂蛋! 我不明白!
I don't feel like coloring eggs! I don't get it!
他这是怎么了?!
What is wrong with him?!
他长大了, Randy.
Well, he's just getting older, Randy.
也许他已经知道了复活节兔子不是真的
Maybe he figured out the Easter bunny isn't real.
你一无所知!
You know so little!
复活节我想要个Baltor玩具兵
And I want a Baltor soldier doll for Easter,
和5辆 Crash'n'Go RC小汽车, 你听懂了没?!
and five Crash'n'Go RC cars, you got that?!
你能办到吗?!
Do you HAVE that?!
- 啊啊, 你不觉得这有点太- - 不不! 你不能问我问题!
- Ahh, don't you think that's- - Nono! You don't ask me questions!
你是兔子! 我是人.
You are a rabbit! I am a human.
如果复活节你不能给我这些 我就宰了你!
So if you don't bring me what I want for Easter, I can fucking kill you!
笑!
Smile!
88, 复活节兔子!
Bye, Easter bunny!
噢 上帝.
Oh My God.
那么, 你能不能解释下这到底怎么回事?
All right, can you explain to me what's going on?
啊?
Huh?
给蛋涂颜色然后你把它们藏起来
What is the deal with the coloring the eggs and you hiding them and all that?
这些和耶稣死在十字架上有什么关系?
What does that have to do with Jesus dying on the Cross?
有象征意义吗?
It is symbolic?
你是不是在暗示圣经里的故事?
Are you trying to reference something that happened in Biblical times?
回答我!
Answer me!
你看, 孩子 恩, 我,我只不过是个演员.
Look, kid ahh, I'm j-, I'm just a guy in a costume.
我知道!
I know that!
但是我觉得你应该知道一些复活节的事情
But I figure you must have some knowledge of what Easter's about
因为你在这商场里表演复活节兔子!
if you're playing the Easter Bunny at the mall!
复活节就是复活节. 一个节日而已,孩子.
Easter's just Easter. Just, just go with it, kid.
不, 我不会就这么算了! 我要知道这背后到底有什么!
NO, I'm not gonna just go with it! I'm gonna find out what's behind all this!
我想休息下. 可以吗?
I need a break. Can I have a break?
出事了.
We have a problem.
有人要调查我们.
Somebody's onto us.
是的, 他问了许多问题.
Yeah, he's askin' a lot of questions.
他能不能找到复活节的秘密只是个时间问题了.
Only a matter of time before he finds out what Easter's really about.
好, 我明白要干什么.
Yes, I understand what must be done.
通知其他人.
Call the others.
妈? 爸?
Mom? Dad?
有人在家吗??
Anybody home??
等会, Stanley, 我在厕所!
Not now, Stanley, I'm on the toilet!
- 爸! 救救我! - 等会, 我在大便.
- Dad! You've gotta help me! - Hang on, I'm taking a crap.
爸! 复活节兔子在追我!
Dad! There's Easter bunnies chasing me!
什么?
What?
他们从商场一直追到这里! 我不知道他们要干什么
They chased me from the mall! I don't know what they want!
他们进来了! 爸, 开门!
They're coming in! Dad, open the DOOR!
Dad??
我们...得谈谈, Stan.
We... need to talk, Stan.
没事了,兄弟们
Ih, it's okay guys.
- Randy? - 对.
- Randy? - Yeah.
因为那孩子就是我儿子
'Cause it turns out the kid we're after is my son.
哦.
Ohhh.
告诉Grand 这里没事了.
Tell the Grand Hare everything is okay.
我会搞定的.
I'll take it from here.
我原本不想告诉你, Stan.
I wanted to keep this from you, Stan.
我想等你长大些,但是...
I really wanted to wait until you were older but...
你一直在纠缠那个问题!
you just had to keep asking questions!
为什么这些人要追我?!
Why were those other rabbit guys chasing me?!
我们以为有人在调查我们 我们必须得小心.
We have to be careful when we think somebody's onto us.
我们属于一个秘密组织, Stan.
We are all part of a secret society, Stan.
一个非常古老的,非常重要的组织
A very ancient, very important society of men
沿着兔子的足迹, 守护着复活节兔子的秘密
who follow the way of the Rabbit, and protect the secret of the Easter bunny.
我们称为野兔男俱乐部(the Hare Club For Men).
We are called... the Hare Club For Men.
妈妈知道这个吗?
Does Mom know about this?
不, 这是野兔"男"俱乐部. 女人们是不会明白的.
Duh, it's the Hare Club For Men. Chicks wouldn't understand.
我也不明白!
I don't understand!
我属于一个已经成立了上千年的秘密组织!
I belong to a secret society that has been around for thousands of years!
我们不能透露身份!
Our identities have to be protected!
你能,你能拿,拿掉耳朵吗?
Could, could you, take off, the ears, please?
Stan, 你好象还没明白这事的严重性!
Stan, you don't seem to understand how serious this is!
我们所守护的复活节秘密
The secret of Easter that we protect
足可以颠覆整个世界!
is something that could rock the foundation of the entire world!
那么复活节秘密是什么?
So what is the secret of Easter?
我不能告诉你. 你必须先加入这个组织, 但是...
I can't tell you. You have to be allowed into the Society first, but...
但是也许... 是时候了.
but perhaps... it's time.
我早知道这一天会来的,
I always knew this day would come,
我的儿子会加入这个组织
when my son would be brought into the society.
这让我想起我父亲把我带进这个组织的那一天.
Reminds me of the day I was brought in by my father.
- 爷爷也在里面? - 当然了.
- Grandpa's in it too? - Of course.
Marshe家族在这里面已经有好几代人了.
Marshes have been in the Hare Club For Men for generations.
现在又回到了起点.
All the way back to the beginning.
爸, 我要一直戴着这个包吗?
Dad, do I have to wear this bag over my head the entire time?
你现在还不是会员. 不能让你知道秘密会议的地点.
You aren't a member yet. You can't know where our secret meetings take place.
我们要走好一段路
We're going to a distant location,
一个湖旁的老房子,大概40分钟路程
an old building near a lake about 40 minutes away.
你是说 old Galveston Lodge?
You mean the old Galveston Lodge?
见鬼.
Damnit.
- 嘿 Bill. - Evenin' Marcus.
- Hey Bill. - Evenin' Marcus.
- 嘿嘿嘿, 看看你! - 大家好.
- Heh heh hey, look at you! - Hey everybody.
Stan Marsh, 欢迎! 你肯定很兴奋.
Stan Marsh, welcome! You must be very excited.
我肯定?
Must I?
他来了! 那是我孙子!
There he is! There's my grandson!
- 嗨 爷爷. - 我为你骄傲, Billy.
- Hi Grandpa. - I'm proud of ya, Billy.
...我是Stan.
...Stan.
今晚,我们要决定一个新成员 能不能守护这个秘密
Tonight, we determine if a new member is worthy of protecting the Secret.
有请... 兔子.
Bring out... the rabbit.
Sanctum Piter oteum, Deus ore uneum.
Hippitus hoppitus reus homine.
In suspiratoreum, lepus in re sanctum.
Hippitus hoppitus Deus Domine.
向可爱的兔子下跪,雪球!
All hail the cute rabbit, Snowball!
雪球万岁.
Hail Snowball.
Stan Marsh,
你准备好了来听复活节的秘密了吗?
are you ready to hear the secret of Easter?
- 是的. - 你肯定, 孩子?
- Yeah. - Are you sure, son?
一旦你知道了秘密, 你将永远属于这个组织.
Once you hear the secret, you will be bound to The Hare Club For Men forever.
是的, 我准备好了.
Yeah, I wanna know already.
非常好.
Very well.
最后的晚餐,上帝召见了他的12个门徒.
At the Last Supper, Jesus Christ met with his 12 Disciples.
就在那一刻
It was there that-
- 他们来了! - 保护雪球!
- They found us! - Protect Snowball!
他们人太多了!
They're everywhere!
来, 我们得离开这!
Come on, we've gotta go!
Stan, 带上雪球快跑!
Stan, take Snowball and get out of here!
- 往哪跑? - 快跑!!!
- Where am I supposed to go? - JUST GET OUT OF HERE!!!
兔子哪去了?!
Where is the rabbit?!
你带我们去哪??
Where are you taking us??
不! 我哪也不去!
No! I'm not goin' anywhere!
上帝啊!
Jesus Christ!
你把兔子给谁了?!
Who did you give the rabbit to?!
搜查这里! 那孩子走不了多远!
Search the area! The boy could not have gotten far!
噢 不...
Oh no...
救命.
Help.
怎么了?
What happened?
我爸在一个叫"野兔男俱乐部"的组织里
My Dad's in a rabbit-worshiping cult called the Hare Club For Men
他们守护着复活节的秘密 但是就在他们要告诉我这秘密的时候
they protect the secret of Easter but before they said what it was
有一群忍者闯了进来 他们要我带走雪球.
they were attacked by ninjas and put me in charge of Snowball.
...我正在玩手指涂鸦.
...I'm kind of fingerpainting right now.
兄弟, 他们抓了我爸. 他们还杀了几个人.
Dude, they took my Dad away. They even shot one of his fellow hares.
而且现在他们在追我!
And now they're after me!
你知道复活节吗?
Do you know anything about Easter?
耶稣,兔子,彩蛋这之间到底有什么联系?
What is the connection between Jesus and rabbits and colored eggs?
兄弟, 我信犹太教的. 我不知道.
Dude, I'm Jewish. I have no idea.
Nelson.
Nelson? Nelson, 回答我.
Nelson? Nelson, say something.
我的腿. 可能断了.
My legs. I... I think they're broken.
Nelson, 你知道我们在哪吗? 他们把我们带到哪了?
Nelson, do you know where we are? Where did they take us?
不知道... 我们走了好几个小时... 一路都是黑的 ...
Don't know... we traveled for hours... kept blacking out...
你...
You...
嗨, 我们想和Teabag教授谈谈
Hi, we'd like to speak to a Professor Teabag?
- 谈什么? - 复活节的历史.
- What is it in regard to? - The history of Easter.
抱歉孩子们, 现在上课有点迟了.
Sorry boys, it's a little late for me to be giving lectures.
求您了? 你知道野兔男俱乐部吗?
Please? Do you know anything about the Hare Club For Men?
守护者? 秘密的守护者?
The Keepers? The Guardians of the Secret?
我爸是. 这只... 兔子也是.
My Dad is in it. This... rabbit is too somehow.
进来吧.
Come on in.
野兔男俱乐部已经有几个世纪了.
The Hare Club For Men has been around for centuries.
其中最有名的成员是达芬奇(Leonardo da Vinci).
One of its most famous members was Leonardo da Vinci.
看看<<最后的晚餐>>( the Last Supper).
Behold the Last Supper.
在耶稣被钉死之前和他的门徒们的晚餐
The dinner Christ had with his disciples the night before he was crucified.
看看桌子上有什么食物?
What food do you see on the table?
- 只有面包... - 真的?
- Just bread... - Really?
看看耶稣的右边.
Look to Jesus' right.
这个东西和其他的颜色有点不同.
The food which is a little different color than the others.
有点象... 鸡蛋.
It kind of looks like... an egg.
是的. 鸡蛋暗示了秘密.
Yes. The egg marks the secret.
它就放在Saint Peter的正前方.
It lies directly in front of... Saint Peter.
Saint Peter是谁?
Who is Saint Peter?
他是耶稣的门徒, 第一个由耶稣指任为教皇的门徒
He was the disciple that Jesus made into the first pope.
是的.
Eggsactly.
但是这里有教会没有告诉你们的事.
But there's something the Church didn't tell you.
实际上, Peter 根本就不是人.
In actuality, Peter wasn't a man at all.
Saint Peter... 是一只兔子.
Saint Peter... was a rabbit.
Peter 兔.
Peter Rabbit.
当然, 教会不会让达芬奇把他画成一只兔子
Of course, the Church wouldn't allow da Vinci to paint Peter as a rabbit,
所以把他画成了一个人, 但是留下了线索. 看近点.
so he painted him as a man, but left clues. Look closely.
- 我没看见. - 再看近点.
- I don't see it. - Look closelier.
- 他看起来象是个人. - 再看近点.
- He looks like a guy. - Look more closelier.
使用激光技术 我们可以看到画下面的东西,
With laser technology we can look beneath the paint,
达芬奇最先画上去的东西.
the way da Vinci originally painted it.
这就是...Saint Peter.
That... is Saint Peter.
基督教的第一个教皇.
The original Pope of Christianity.
我不信.
I don't believe it.
证据很多. 看看教皇的帽子 看起来一点也不合适
Proof is everywhere. Look at the Pope's hat. It makes no sense,
除非它是为兔子设计的 就好看多了
except that it was originally designed... for a rabbit.
但是为什么耶稣会让兔子来管理教会?
But why would Jesus want a rabbit to run his church?
因为耶稣知道所有教会里的人
Because Jesus knew no one man
都不可能没有私心.
could speak for everyone in a religion.
人类很自私; 兔子则不会.
Men can be intolerant; rabbits are pure.
但是天主教掩埋了真相, 用一个人替换了兔子
But the Catholic Church buried the truth, put a man in charge,
然后野兔男俱乐部从此开始涂蛋
and the Hare Club For Men has been decorating eggs ever since
为了让秘密在达芬奇的画中延续.
to keep the secret in da Vinci's painting alive.
所以梵蒂冈抓了Stan的爸爸?
So... the Vatican took Stan's dad?
你怎么可以告诉人们St. Peter是一只兔子
You dare to mock God by telling people St. Peter was a rabbit?
你这怪物! 你无权戴这个帽子!
You monster! You have no right to wear that hat!
说St. Peter是兔子是对神的亵渎!
Trying to tell people that St. Peter was a rabbit is blasphemy!
你必须认罪,否则你将在地狱被烧死!
You must admit you are wrong or burn in hell!
说耶稣让兔子管理教会
It's saying stupid things like that
是一件很蠢的事.
that made Jesus wanna put a rabbit in charge.
很抱歉我没能给您抓到兔子,教皇殿下
I'm sorry I couldn't bring you the rabbit, Your Holiness,
但是他们知道在哪!
but they know where it is!
你们那只叫雪球的兔子对基督教是个威胁
The rabbit you call Snowball is a threat to Christ's Church.
它在哪?!
Where is the rabbit?!
我不知道!而且就算我知道...
I don't know! And even if I did know...
呃, 我应该会告诉你们 因为我不想再待在这里了.
well, I'd probably tell you because I don't wanna be here anymore.
- 带他去用刑! - 用刑, 呃, 但是 Bill,
- Take him to be tortured! - Tortured, huh, but Bill,
所有这些事...用刑,忍者 看起来好象不是基督教的做法
all this... torturing and ninjas, it just doesn't seem very Christian.
是你在请求美国天主教联盟的帮助
You asked for the help of the American Catholic League,
交给我们来干! 带走他!
let us do our job! Take him!
不! 不, 你这个兔崽子! 别动我!
No! No, you bunny-hating bastards! Don't do this!
我不明白. 为什么教皇抓我爸当人质?
I don't get it. Why would the pope be holding my Dad hostage for Snowball?
我认为雪球一定是St. Peter的后代
I believe Snowball must be a direct descendant of St. Peter himself,
而且是教皇皇位的真正继承人
and therefor the true heir of the pope's throne.
Mr. Teabag! 快走!
Mr. Teabag! Get out!
- 他们来了! - 孩子们, 快跑!
- They found me! - Boys, get out of here!
跑到树林去! 我会给你们争取些时间.
Head to the woods! I'll try to buy you some time.
检查楼上!
Check upstairs!
楼上clear! 检查办公室!
Upstairs clear! Try the office!
在这里!
In here!
这是什么?
What's that?
PEEEEPS!
现在怎么办?
So what now?
如果教皇抓了我爸...
If the pope has my Dad...
我只好给他想要的东西了.
I have to give him what he wants.
你不是要把雪球给他们吧?
You aren't just gonna hand Snowball over?
我有选择吗?! 没人可以帮我们!
What choice do I have?! There's nobody left who can help us!
等等...
Wait...
除非...
unless...
也许.
maybe there is.
来, 拿着.
Here, hold this.
上帝,
Jesus,
我知道我们很长时间没聊过了,
I know we haven't talked in a long time,
而且每次总聊的我想杀了你, 但是...
and I know that every time you appear we end up killing you somehow, but...
我不知道该怎么办.
I don't know what to do.
你能帮我吗.
And I could really use your help.
这兔子刚才在我衣服上拉屎了.
I think the rabbit just crapped on my jacket.
狂欢吧,梵蒂冈 这是我们的复活节之夜.
Live, from the Vatican, it's our Easter Vigil coverage.
神圣的星期六就要结束了, 梵蒂冈的复活节之夜开始了.
As Holy Saturday comes to an end, the Easter vigil at the Vatican begins.
数千人来到这里会见教皇然后庆祝复活节
Thousand have turned out to hear the Pope and celebrate the Resurrection.
在这个复活节之夜教皇也将展示他的仁慈
For this Easter vigil the Pope is also showing his divine grace
施舍穷人食物, 一大锅的炖兔肉.
by feeding the poor, with a massive rabbit stew.
不!
NOOO!
不!别, 不要
Noo! No, don't put m-
Bill, 做的太过头了.
Bill, this seems extreme.
必须让那个带着雪球的孩子知道
The child who has the rabbit has to know
如果他不把兔子给我们,我们就杀掉人质.
that we are willing to kill the hostages if he doesn't hand it over.
教皇殿下, 有一个带着兔子的孩子求见!
Your Holiness, a child has arrived witha the rabbit!
你看?
Ya see?
噢 感谢上帝!
Oh thank God!
给他们, Stan! 他们要杀我! 把兔子给他们!
Hand it over, Stan! They're gonna kill me! Give them the rabbit!
是的,给我们!
Yes, hand it over!
首先, 你得保证不会伤害它!
First, you have to promise you won't hurt it!
还有你会放了所有人
And that you'll let everybody go!
- 我们保证. - 我们发誓, 对着十字架发誓.
- We promise. - We swear it, on the cross.
给他们兔子, STAN!!
JUST HAND OVER THE BUNNY, STAN!!
好的, 好的.
Okay, fine.
Stanley, 你干嘛那么做?
Stanley, why did you do that?
我情愿为兔子死掉.
I would have proudly died for that rabbit.
- 是你说 "给兔子"的 - 不!
- You said "hand over the bunny." - No!
以后你得换个方式来回忆这事
That is NOT the way we're remembering it!
带他们下去!
Take them into custody!
嘿, 怎么回事!
Hey, what the hell!
Bill, 我们得到兔子了, 不需要别的了.
Bill, we have zeh rabbit, it's all we need.
别太软弱, 教皇殿下!
Don't be soft, Your Holiness!
这些"异教徒"必须在众人面前接受惩罚!
These "whores" must be punished in front of everyone!
你对着十字架发誓的, 混蛋!
You swore on the cross, fatso!
是的. 但很不幸的是...
Yeah. Too bad for you...
我有2个十字架!
it was a double cross!
噢, 我们早该料到了!
Oh, we should've seen that coming!
Bill, 恐怕2个十字架不是基督教的做法
Bill, I'm not sure that double crossing people is very Christian.
就算是耶稣也会这么干的!
IT IS WHAT CHRIST WOULD'VE WANTED!
谁让你这么说的?!
Who are you to say that?!
不... 可能.
It... can't be.
上帝!
Jesus!
He is risen. He is risen.
Let the voices sing his praises on this holy day.
He is risen!
上帝, 我们以为你死了. 在伊拉克.
Jesus, we thought you died. In Iraq.
我有复活的本事. 你忘了吗?
I have the power of resurrection. Or have you forgotten?
看起来你们忘记了很多事情.
You all seem to have forgotten a lot of things.
上帝,你听到我的祈祷了!
Jesus, you did answer my prayer!
事实上, 我听到的是Nick Donovan的祈祷.
Actually, I was answering the prayer of Nick Donovan.
噢, 是我  太棒了!
Ohh, that's me Neato!
这就是我让兔子管理教会的原因!
This is exactly why I put a rabbit in charge of the Church, Benedictus!
人太容易走错路了.
Because men are so easily led astray.
St. Peter 是一只兔子. 一只该当教皇的兔子.
St. Peter was a rabbit. And a rabbit should be Pope.
- 杀了他! - 什么?!
- Kill him! - WHAT?!
他反对教会. 他必须死!
He goes against the Church. He must die!
好吧, 这样做的话, Bill.
All right, that does it, Bill.
我很肯定杀了上帝不是基督教的做法.
I'm pretty sure that killing Jesus is not very Christian.
你这懦夫! 你逼我的,抓住他们!
You are soft! Weak! You leave me no choice: take them!
你干什么?!
What are you doing?!
我是教皇!
I am the Pope!
你可以下台了!
You are no longer able to fulfill your duties to the Lord!
复活节之夜会照计划进行!
The Easter vigil will go on as planned!
所有野兔男成员, 大人和小孩,
Every Hare Club member, young and old,
会看着他们的救世主死掉!
will watch as their precious savior dies!
你有毛病吗, 老兄?!
What is your problem, guy?!
把这2个犹太人关起来! 等会处置他们.
Lock up those two Jews! We'll deal with them later.
别! 别!
No! No!
梵蒂冈发生了些奇怪的事
A strange turn of events here at the Vatican:
教皇Benedictus退位了,
Pope Benedictus has stepped down,
取而代之的是...新教皇Bill Donohue
ushering the new era of... Pope Bill Donohue
我们的人民!
My people!
我将以炖兔子肉开始复活节
This Easter I'm gonna start by making our rabbit stew
大量的炖兔子肉!
ten times meatier!
不!听我说! 我们不是兔子!
No! Listen! We aren't rabbits!
原谅我, 上帝.
Forgive me, Jesus.
我们来不及阻止他了!
We'll never get out in time to stop him!
你没有什么超能力了吗?
Don't you have any superpowers?
作为一个凡人我没有.除非我死了.
Not as a mortal. Only in death.
等等. 有办法了.
Wait. That's it.
我们没有选择了, Kyle. 你必须得杀了我.
We have no choice, Kyle. You're going to have to kill me.
- 什么?? - 用这个捅我.
- What?? - Stab me with this.
我死了就能在外面复活了.
If I die I can resurrect outside the bars.
不行! 你自己捅.
N-no way! Do it yourself.
自杀是一种亵渎. 没有选择了, Kyle!
Suicide is blasphemy. There's no choice here, Kyle!
兄弟, 你不明白, 我是犹太人. 犹太人不能杀上帝.
Dude, you don't understand, I'm a Jew. I have a few hangups about killing Jesus.
快点吧. 对着脖子捅. 我会马上复活的.
Just make it quick. Through the neck. I'll arise again immediately.
别逼我.
Don't make me do this.
孩子,没时间了! 捅!
My son, there is no time! DO IT!
永远别让Eric Cartman 知道这个.
Eric Cartman can never know about this.
我明白. 还有 Kyle,
I understand. And Kyle,
- 复活节快乐. - 复活节快乐, 上帝.
- happy Easter. - Happy Easter, Jesus.
...上帝?
...Jesus?
看吧, 再也不会有复活节兔子和彩蛋了!
Behold, no longer will Easter be about bunnies and colored eggs!
杀了这兔子!
Kill the rabbit!
很遗憾, 小兔子.
Sorry, little bunny.
雪球!
Snowball!
上帝?
Jesus?
别!
Stop!
那兔子是圣灵的后代!
That rabbit is of holy descent!
你就不能离远点?!
Why won't you go away?!
教会不能只由一个人主宰!
One man cannot be the voice of the Church!
我受够了这亵渎! 我现在是教皇!
Enough of this blasphemy! I'm the Pope now!
我是上帝的代言人!!
That means I am the voice of God!!
不再是了. 我要解雇你.
Not anymore. I'm removing you from your position.
耶!!!
YAAAY!!!
太棒了 上帝!
All right Jesus!
Sanctum Piter oteum, Deus ore uneum.
Hippitus hoppitus reus homine.
教皇殿下,
Your Holiness,
我们该如何告诉世人们怎样过好生活
what should we tell the world about how to run their lives?
它不说话.
It isn't saying anything.
是的, 就象上帝安排的那样.
Yes, just as a-Jesus intended it.
Stanley, 我为你骄傲.
Stanley, I'm so proud of you.
这个复活节你学到了不少东西.
You've learned so very much this Easter.
是的. 我学会了不要问问题.
Yeah. I've learned not to ask questions.
只管涂蛋,还有闭上我的嘴.
Just dye the eggs and keep my mouth shut.
这才是我的儿子.
That's my boy.
Hippitus hoppitus Deus Domine.